bexar.org 2018-09-25

# Privacy Policy | Bexar County, TX - Official Website

Bexar County Web Privacy Statement  

Bexar County Information Services maintains the Bexar County Web site as a public service. The following is the privacy policy for the site including all pages starting with www.bexar.org/ and www.bexar.org/.

  1. We do not use cookies to collect information. Note: A cookie file contains unique information a web site can use to track such things as passwords, lists of pages you’ve visited, and the date when you last looked at a specific page or to identify your session at a particular web site. A cookie is often used in commercial sites to identify the items selected for a specific shopping cart application.
  2. If you send us an electronic mail message with a question or comment that contains personally identifying information, or fill out a form that e-mails us this information, we will only use the personally-identifiable information to respond to your request and analyze trends. We may redirect your message to another government agency or person who is in a better position to answer your question, or benefit from your comments.
  3. All electronic mail messages delivered to a Bexar County employee, office, elected official or any other governmental entity, are subject to the Texas Public Information Act. This means that the messages received are subject to possible disclosure to any person making an appropriate request to see such information, pursuant to the Act. 
  4. For site management functions, information, as described below, regarding any access to the Bexar County Web site is collected for analysis and statistical purposes. This information is not reported or used in any manner that would reveal personally identifiable information, and will not be released to any outside parties unless legally required to do so.

We use Log analysis tools to create summary statistics, which are used for purposes such as assessing what information is of most interest, determining technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas. The following information is collected for this analysis:

>  **User Client hostname** \- The hostname (or IP address if DNS is disabled) of the user/client requesting access.  
>  **HTTP header, "user-agent"** \- The user-agent information includes the type of browser, its version, and the operating system it's running on.  
>  **HTTP header, "referrer"** \- The referrer specifies the page from which the client accessed the current page.  
>  **System date** \- The date and time of the user/client request.  
>  **Full request** \- The exact request the user/client made.  
>  **Status** \- The status code the server returned to the user/client.  
>  **Content length** \- The content length, in bytes, of the document sent to the user/client.  
>  **Method** \- The request method used.  
>  **Universal Resource Identifier (URI)** \- The location of a resource on the server.  
>  **Query string of the URI** \- Anything after the question mark in a URI.  
>  **Protocol** \- The transport protocol and version used.  
> 

If you have any questions or comments on our Policy, please address them to the [Bexar County Webmaster](mailto:webmaster@bexar.org)
